FRANSISKUS ALDO

WEB DEVELOPER

During my 1.5 years of work experience as a data processor, I gained an interest in web development technology. My passion is to reach out to the global community through building web applications. As a full-stack developer, I hope to bridge the access to all, whether for UX or clean back-end code. I have attended numerous independent online courses related to it, but in the end, Lighthouse Labs Coding Bootcamp is the one that gave me a proper pathway to learn efficiently. through adaptability, resilience, and fast pace 12-week curriculum.

PROJECTS

Haime

Haime is an Online Store App. It's a full-stack application with React as a front-end and Python Django as a back-end REST API

Ez-League

Collaboration Project with my 2 other colleagues. Ez-League is a Sports League manager App. with React Front End, Tailwind CSS, Express JS, and PostgreSQL

Jungle-Project

Its an E-Commerce App. Legacy Code with Ruby on Rails, for Learn, debugging, and adding a new feature.

Interview Scheduler

Interview Scheduler is a single-page React app for booking and also scheduling the interview.

Once Upon A Book

Once Upon A Book is a bookstore website. Collaboration Project with my 2 other colleagues. this App build with Express JS and EJS with PostgreSQL

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES: Javascript, Ruby, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS

FRAMEWORKS / LIBRARIES:

NodeJS, React, Express, Rails, Django, Axios, Jquery, AJAX, EJS, SASS, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, Tailwind

TESTING: Mocha and Chai, Storybook, Jest, Cypress, Rspec

TOOLS: Git, Github

LANGUAGE: English, Indonesian

OTHER: Googling

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs

Diploma Web Development 2022

Atma Jaya University

Bachelor Management of Economics 2011

Aug. 2006 - July 2011

Jan. 2022 - Apr. 2022

EMPLOYMENT

Index Exchange, Quality Assurance Analyst, Remote

Aug. 2021 - June 2022

- Following Instruction and guidelines to ensure compliance with Index Exchange policies and quality standards.
- Attention to detail in flagging sensitive content which may be graphic, violent, or hateful, including offensive or derogatory language or other potential distressing material before approving the advertisement content
- Categorize advertisements based on brand, industry, and content group
- Effective communication to provide information, educate customers to update trackers, update required applications & tools and keep internal stakeholders informed of new issues

Cognizant Technology Solution Canada Inc, Senior Data Processor, Toronto Mar. 2018 -July 2019

- Leading sub-team consist 5 people.
- Review social media content based on social media client requirements.
- Conduct research and provide insight to identify trends for the social media client(s), provide input to information systems professionals regarding the collection, validity, and suitability of data
- Understand policies and implement them on a variety of workflows, research, and document requirements, data collection, and policy
- Work closely with internal teams as well as external clients to balance the day-to-day service/support of customers

- Work and analyze data to help the client develop new policy
- Represent sub-team to coordinate with Team Leader
- Keep the client aware of the trend through weekly insight reports using Microsoft Excel